netherlandsfoundation.org.nz 2014-06-19

# Privacy Policy : New Zealand Netherlands Foundation

This privacy policy applies to personal information (as that term is defined in the Privacy Act 1993) and other information collected by the New Zealand Netherlands Foundation (NZNF) on [netherlandsfoundation.org.nz](http://www.netherlandsfoundation.org.nz/) ('this website'). In this privacy policy, the terms 'we', 'us', and 'our' refer to the NZNF. Your use of this website is governed by our terms of use. This privacy policy must be read in conjunction with our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.netherlandsfoundation.org.nz/terms-and-conditions/) statement.

## Information provided by you

If you have registered with us as a supporter, sponsor or advertiser and unless you indicated on the form you did not wish to receive information from us, being on our database means you will be eligible to receive information from sponsors about events and special offers from time to time. Any information provided by you will be used only for communicating with you and will be held in a secure database.

## Automated data collection

When you visit this website, we may use automated tools (such as cookies, sessions, and usage monitoring software) to collect certain information regarding visitors to our website including (without limitation):

  * your internet protocol address
  * what website you came from to get here
  * the day, date and time of your visit
  * how long you stay for
  * what pages you visited, and
  * what kind of computer and browser you are using.

We collect and log this information for statistical purposes. This information will be used in aggregate form to analyse how this website is being used. This data will not be used to identify individuals or any personal information.

This website uses cookies and sessions to track data and record information about visitor behaviour. A cookie is a piece of code that creates a file on your computer to track the pages that you view on our website. This information is collected so that we may provide you with a better website resource. The aggregate data is collected and used to create content reports that will help us understand which parts of our website are performing well and which pages are most popular so we can focus on the areas important to you.

You may turn off cookies at any time. Most browsers have a feature that allows the user to refuse cookies or issues a warning when cookies are being sent - check your browser's "Help". Turning off cookies will not affect your ability to use this website. If you have any questions, please [email us](mailto:executive.director@netherlandsfoundation.org.nz).

You may browse and access this website without providing any personal information. You may voluntarily provide personal information to us (e.g. through email feedback, or by requesting to be notified when new material is published). We will only use and disclose your personal information to communicate with you, provide services to you, and otherwise in accordance with the Privacy Act 1993. We will endeavour to keep such information secure. You consent to receiving electronic messages and information sent by us (or on our behalf) for any purposes described in this privacy policy.

## Changes to our privacy policy

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy from time to time by publishing the revised privacy policy on our website. Please check this privacy policy regularly for modifications and updates. If you continue to use this website or if you provide any personal information after we post changes to this privacy policy, this is deemed to be your acceptance of any such changes.

## Third party websites

This website contains hyperlinks to websites operated by third parties. We are not responsible for the manner in which those websites collect, store, use, and distribute any personal information you provide. When you visit third party websites from hyperlinks displayed on this website, we encourage you to review the privacy statements of those websites so that you can understand how the personal information you provide may be collected, stored, used and distributed.

## Concerns or feedback

If you wish to request access to, or correction of, any personal information held by us or you have concerns about the personal information we hold, please [email our privacy officer](mailto:executive.director@netherlandsfoundation.org.nz).

Or write to our privacy officer:

The Privacy Officer  
New Zealand Netherlands Foundation  
PO Box 5353  
Wellington 6145
